Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 6 5583/6
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 6
1917-1973
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Princeton University Industrial Relations Section
5583/6
88.33 cubic feet
86.3 linear ft.
Records, publications.
9125180
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, November 01, 2007
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, March 25, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5880: Archives Organization File V, Additional Company Documents 5583/1: Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 1 5583/2: Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 2 5583/3: Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 3 5583/4: Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 4. Corporate and Organizational Publications 5583/5: Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 5 5956: Archives Organization File Additional records
Industrial relations -- United States -- Sources.; Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives.; Armco Inc.; British Institute of Management; Scovill Manufacturing Company; Campbell Soup Company; Canadian National Railways; Chesapeake and Ohio Railway Company; Pere Marquette Railway; New York, Chicago & St. Louis Railroad; Chester M. Wright and Associates; Colgate & Company; United States. Department of Labor; AFL-CIO; New York (State). Department of Labor; Manufacturers Association of Connecticut; Connecticut Business and Industry Association; General Electric Company. Erie Works; Delaware and Hudson Railway Company; Automobile Manufacturers Association; National Foremen's Institute; H.J. Heinz Company; General Electric Company. Switchgear Divisions; Lockheed-California Company; New Departure Company; New York (State). Public Employment Relations Board; Pennsylvania Railroad; Dupont (Ind.); Chase Manhattan Bank; Norton Company; Fairchild News Service; Swift & Company; Trade Union Courier Publishing; John A. Roebling's Sons Company; Distributing, Processing and Office Workers of America; United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America; Black and Decker Manufacturing; National Industrial Conference Board; Connecticut Business and Industry Association; Commonwealth Edison Company; American Communications Association; National Union of Railwaymen (Great Britain); Federal Reserve Club of New York; John B. Stetson Hat Company; Prudential Insurance Company of America; Illinois Central Railroad Company; United States. Railroad Retirement Board; Amalgamated Association of Street, Electric Railway and Motor Coach Employees of America; Pennsylvania Railroad; Nashville, Chattanooga, and St. Louis Railway; New York Central Lines; Connecticut General Life Insurance Company; National Founders Association; National Metal Trades Association (U.S.); International Brotherhood of Paper Makers; Peoples Gas Light and Coke Company; Pere Marquette Railway; Owens-Illinois Glass Company; National Retail Dry Goods Association (U.S.); National Association of Foremen; Rochester Gas and Electric Corporation; Chicago Great Western Railroad Company; United Cloth Hat and Cap Makers of North America; Central Hudson Gas and Electric Corporation; Baltimore and Ohio Railroad Company; Railway Express Agency; Standard Oil Company of California; International Labor Press of America; General Electric Company; New Jersey Bell Telephone Company; Lever Brothers Company; Pullman Company; Texas Company
9125180
- Armco (American Rolling Mill Company), 1936-1945 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Arm-Co Operator, 1936-1945 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Scope and Contents
    Author: Armco (American Rolling Mill Company)
    Notes: Bound volume.
    Format: Publication
    Language: English.
- Armco (American Rolling Mill Company), 1946-1951 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Arm-Co Operator, 1946-1951 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Notes: January, 1946-December, 1951. Bound volume.
- British Institute of Management, 1947-1952 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: British Management Review, 1947-1952 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Author: Institute of Industrial Administration
    Notes: v.6 (1947)-v.10 (1952). Bound volume.
- British Institute of Management, 1952-1955 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: British Management Review, 1952-1955 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.11 (1952)-v.13 (1955). Bound volume.
- British Institute of Management, 1956-1957 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: British Management Review, 1956-1957 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.14 (1956)-v.15 (1957). Bound volume.
- Scovill Manufacturing Company, 1941-1943 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: The Bulletin (Scovill Manufacturing Company), 1941-1943 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    Author: Scovill Manufacturing Company
    Notes: v.20 (1941)-v.24 (1943). Bound volume.
- Scovill Manufacturing Company, 1944-1946 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: The Bulletin (Scovill Manufacturing Company), 1944-1946 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.25 (1944)-v.29 (1946). Bound volume.
- Scovill Manufacturing Company, 1946-1949 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: The Bulletin (Scovill Manufacturing Company), 1946-1949 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.30 (1946)-v.33 (1949). Bound volume.
- Campbell Soup Company, 1947-1955 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Campbell People, 1947-1955 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    Author: Campbell Soup Company
    Notes: v.1:no.2 (1947:Nov.)-v.8:no.11 (1955:Aug.). Bound volume.
- Campbell Soup Company, 1957-1961 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Campbell People, 1957-1961 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    Notes: January, 1957- June, 1961. Bound volume.
- Canadian National Railways, 1924-1925 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Canadian National Railways Magazine, 1924-1925 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    Author: Canadian National Railways
    Notes: v.10 (1924)-v.11 (1925). Bound volume.
- Canadian National Railways, 1926; Publication (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Canadian National Railways Magazine, 1926; Publication (Box 5, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.12:no.1-6 (1926). Bound volume.
- Canadian National Railways, 1926; Publication (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Canadian National Railways Magazine, 1926; Publication (Box 5, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.12:no.7-12 (1926). Bound volume.
- Canadian National Railways, 1927-1928 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Canadian National Railways Magazine, 1927-1928 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.13 (1927)-v.14 (1928). Bound volume.
- Canadian National Railways, 1929-1930 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Canadian National Railways Magazine, 1929-1930 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.15 (1929)-v.16 (1930). Bound volume.
- Central Hudson Gas and Electric, 1928-1933 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Central Hudson Bulletin, 1928-1933 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    Author: Central Hudson Gas and Electric
    Notes: v.8 (1928)-v.13 (1933). Bound volume.
- C & O (Chesapeake and Ohio Railway), 1923-1924 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Chesapeake and Ohio & Hocking Valley Employes Magazine, 1923-1924 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    Author: Public Relations Department
    Notes: v.8 (1923/1924). Bound volume.
- C & O (Chesapeake and Ohio Railway), 1924-1925 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Chesapeake and Ohio & Hocking Valley Employes Magazine, 1924-1925 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.9 (1924/1925). Bound volume.
- C & O (Chesapeake and Ohio Railway), 1926-1927 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Chesapeake and Ohio & Hocking Valley Employes Magazine, 1926-1927 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.10 (1925/1926)-v.11 (1926/1927). Bound volume.
- C & O (Chesapeake and Ohio Railway), 1927-1928 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Chesapeake and Ohio & Hocking Valley Employes Magazine, 1927-1928 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.12 (1927/1928). Bound volume.
- C & O (Chesapeake and Ohio Railway), 1928; Publication (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Chesapeake and Ohio & Hocking Valley Employes Magazine, 1928; Publication (Box 7, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.13 (1928). Bound volume.
- C & O (Chesapeake and Ohio Railway), 1929; Publication (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Chesapeake and Ohio & Hocking Valley Employes Magazine, 1929; Publication (Box 7, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.14 (1929). Bound volume.
- C & O (Chesapeake and Ohio Railway), 1930; Publication (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Chesapeake and Ohio & Hocking Valley Employes Magazine, 1930; Publication (Box 7, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.15 (1930). Bound volume.
- C & O (Chesapeake and Ohio Railway); Pere Marquette Railway; Nickel Plate Road, 1931-1932 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Chesapeake and Ohio Lines Magazine, 1931-1932 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    Author: C & O (Chesapeake and Ohio Railway)
    Notes: v.16 (1931)-v.17 (1932). Bound volume.
- C & O (Chesapeake and Ohio Railway); Pere Marquette Railway; Nickel Plate Road, 1937-1939 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Chesapeake and Ohio Lines Magazine, 1937-1939 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.22 (1937)-v.24 (1939). Bound volume.
- C & O (Chesapeake and Ohio Railway); Pere Marquette Railway; Nickel Plate Road, 1940-1942 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Chesapeake and Ohio Lines Magazine, 1940-1942 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.25 (1940)-v.27 (1942). Bound volume.
- C & O (Chesapeake and Ohio Railway); Pere Marquette Railway; Nickel Plate Road, 1943; Publication (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Chesapeake and Ohio Lines Magazine, 1943; Publication (Box 8, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.28 (1943). Bound volume.
- Chester M. Wright and Associates, 1936-1939 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Chester Wright's Labor Letter, 1936-1939 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    Author: Chester M. Wright and Associates
- Chester M. Wright and Associates, 1940-1944 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Chester Wright's Labor Letter, 1940-1944 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Chester M. Wright and Associates, 1945-1950 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Chester Wright's Labor Letter, 1945-1950 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Colgate and Company, 1923-1924 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Colgate Clock, 1923-1924 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    Author: Colgate and Company
    Notes: v.6 (1923)-v.7 (1924). Bound volume.
- Colgate and Company, 1925-1926 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Colgate Clock, 1925-1926 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.8 (1925)-v.9 (1926). Bound volume.
- Colgate and Company, 1927-1928 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Colgate Clock, 1927-1928 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.10 (1927)-v.11 (1928). Bound volume.
- United States Department of Labor, 1948-1949 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Collective Bargaining Agreements in New York State, 1948-1949 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    Author: Bureau of Labor Statistics
    Notes: v.1 (1948)-v.2 (1949). Bound volume.
- United States Department of Labor, 1950-1951 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Collective Bargaining Agreements in New York State, 1950-1951 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.3 (1950)-v.4 (1951). Bound volume.
- AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations), 1956; Publication (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Collective Bargaining Reports, AFL-CIO, 1956; Publication (Box 10, Folder 1)
    Author: Department of Research
    Notes: v.1 (1956). Bound volume.
- AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations), 1957; Publication (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Collective Bargaining Reports, AFL-CIO, 1957; Publication (Box 10, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.2:no.1 (1957). Bound volume.
- AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations), 1957-1960 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Collective Bargaining Reports, AFL-CIO, 1957-1960 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.2 (1957)-v.5 (1960). Bound volume.
- New York State Department of Labor, 1957-1958 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Collective Bargaining Settlements in New York State, 1957-1958 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    Author: Division of Research and Statistics
    Notes: v.9 (1957)-v.11 (1958). Bound volume.
- New York State Department of Labor, 1959-1960 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Collective Bargaining Settlements in New York State, 1959-1960 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.12 (1959)-v.13 (1960). Bound volume.
- New York State Department of Labor, 1961-1962 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Collective Bargaining Settlements in New York State, 1961-1962 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.14 (1961)-v.15 (1962). Bound volume.
- Columbia Conserve Company, 1927-1932 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Columbia Cauldron, 1927-1932 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    Author: Columbia Conserve Company
    Notes: v.1:no.1 (1927:feb.)-v.6:no.6/7 (1932:July/Aug.). Bound volume.
- United States Department of Labor, 1954-1958 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Combined Employment and Unemployment Release, 1954-1958 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    Author: United States Department of Labor
    Notes: Press releases. Bound volume.
- National Industrial Conference Board, 1933-1938 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Conference Board Service Letter, 1933-1938 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    Author: National Industrial Conference Board
    Notes: v.6 (1933)-v.11 (1938). Bound volume.
- Connecticut Federation of Labor, 1954-1957 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Newsletter and Legal Bulletin, 1954-1957 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    Author: Connecticut Federation of Labor
    Notes: v.1 (1954)-v.3 (1957). Bound volume.
- Manufacturers Association of Connecticut, 1923-1926 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Connecticut Industry, 1923-1926 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    Author: Manufacturers Association of Connecticut
    Notes: v.1 (1923)-v.4 (1926). Bound volume.
- Manufacturers Association of Connecticut, 1927-1928 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Connecticut Industry, 1927-1928 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.5 (1927)-v.6 (1928). Bound volume.
- Manufacturers Association of Connecticut, 1929-1930 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Connecticut Industry, 1929-1930 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.7 (1929)-v.8 (1930). Bound volume.
- Manufacturers Association of Connecticut, 1931-1934 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Connecticut Industry, 1931-1934 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.9 (1931)-v.12 (1934). Bound volume.
- Manufacturers Association of Connecticut, 1935-1938 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Connecticut Industry, 1935-1938 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.13 (1935)-v.16 (1938). Bound volume.
- Manufacturers Association of Connecticut, 1939-1942 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Connecticut Industry, 1939-1942 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.17 (1939)-v.20 (1942). Bound volume.
- Manufacturers Association of Connecticut, 1943-1946 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Connecticut Industry, 1943-1946 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.21 (1943)-v.24 (1946). Bound volume.
- Manufacturers Association of Connecticut, 1947-1949 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Connecticut Industry, 1947-1949 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.25 (1947)-v.27 (1949). Bound volume.
- Manufacturers Association of Connecticut, 1950-1952 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Connecticut Industry, 1950-1952 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.28 (1950)-v.30 (1952). Bound volume.
- Manufacturers Association of Connecticut, 1953-1955 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Connecticut Industry, 1953-1955 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.31 (1953)-v.33 (1955). Bound volume.
- Manufacturers Association of Connecticut, 1956-1957 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Connecticut Industry, 1956-1957 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.34 (1956)-v.35 (1957). Bound volume.
- Manufacturers Association of Connecticut, 1958; Publication (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Connecticut Industry, 1958; Publication (Box 13, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.36 (1958). Bound volume.
- Manufacturers Association of Connecticut, 1959; Publication (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Connecticut Industry, 1959; Publication (Box 14, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.37 (1959). Bound volume.
- Manufacturers Association of Connecticut, 1960; Publication (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Connecticut Industry, 1960; Publication (Box 14, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.38 (1960). Bound volume.
- Manufacturers Association of Connecticut, 1961; Publication (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Connecticut Industry, 1961; Publication (Box 14, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.39 (1961). Bound volume.
- Manufacturers Association of Connecticut, 1962; Publication (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Connecticut Industry, 1962; Publication (Box 14, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.40 (1962). Bound volume.
- Manufacturers Association of Connecticut, 1963; Publication (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Connecticut Industry, 1963; Publication (Box 14, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.41 (1963). Bound volume.
- Manufacturers Association of Connecticut, 1964; Publication (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Connecticut Industry, 1964; Publication (Box 14, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.42 (1964). Bound volume.
- Manufacturers Association of Connecticut, 1965; Publication (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Connecticut Industry, 1965; Publication (Box 14, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.43 (1965). Bound volume.
- Manufacturers Association of Connecticut, 1966; Publication (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Connecticut Industry, 1966; Publication (Box 15, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.44 (1966). Bound volume.
- Manufacturers Association of Connecticut, 1967; Publication (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Connecticut Industry, 1967; Publication (Box 15, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.45 (1967). Bound volume.
- Manufacturers Association of Connecticut, 1968; Publication (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Connecticut Industry, 1968; Publication (Box 15, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.46 (1968). Bound volume.
- Manufacturers Association of Connecticut, 1969; Publication (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Connecticut Industry, 1969; Publication (Box 15, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.47 (1969). Bound volume.
- Manufacturers Association of Connecticut, 1970; Publication (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Connecticut Industry, 1970; Publication (Box 15, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.48 (1970). Bound volume.
- Connecticut Business and Industry Association, 1971; Publication (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Connecticut Industry, 1971; Publication (Box 15, Folder 6)
    Author: Connecticut Business and Industry Association
    Notes: v.49 (1971). Bound volume.
- Connecticut Business and Industry Association, 1972; Publication (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Connecticut Industry, 1972; Publication (Box 15, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.50 (1972). Bound volume.
- General Electric Company, Erie Works, 1922-1923 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Coupler, 1922-1923 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    Author: Publication Committee
    Notes: v.6 (1922/1923). Bound volume.
- General Electric Company, Erie Works, 1923-1926 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Coupler, 1923-1926 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    Notes: v.7 (1923)-v.9 (1926). Bound volume.
- Delaware and Hudson Railway, 1923-1928 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Craftwise; Mechanical Department Bulletin, 1923-1928 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    Author: Motive Power and Car Departments
    Notes: v.1 (1923)-v.6 (1928). Bound volume.
- Delaware and Hudson Railway, 1929-1934 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Craftwise; Mechanical Department Bulletin, 1929-1934 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.7 (1929)-v.12 (1934). Bound volume.
- Lewis Manufacturing Company, 1926-1942 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Curity Club News, 1926-1942 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    Author: Lewis Manufacturing Company
    Notes: v.5:no.3 (1926:June)-v.24:no.4 (1942:Dec.). Bound volume.
- General Electric Company, Pittsfield Works, 1920-1922 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Current News, 1920-1922 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    Author: General Electric Company, Pittsfield Works
    Notes: January, 1920-August, 1922. Bound volume.
- Automobile Manufacturers Association, 1948-1949 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Current News Digest, 1948-1949 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    Author: Automobile Manufacturers Association
    Notes: no.1 (1948:Apr. 28)-no.40 (1949:Nov. 9). Bound volume.
- Automobile Manufacturers Association, 1949-1951 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Current News Digest, 1949-1951 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    Notes: no.41 (1949:Nov. 22)-no.80 (1951:June 12). Bound volume.
- New York Edison Company, 1926-1927 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Edison Weekly, 1926-1927 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    Author: Contract and Inspection Department
    Notes: v.22 (1926)-v.23 (1927). Bound volume.
- New York Edison Company, 1928; Publication (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Edison Weekly, 1928; Publication (Box 17, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.24 (1928). Bound volume.
- Bureau of Personnel Administration, 1934-1938 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Employer - Employee Relations, 1934-1938 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    Author: Bureau of Personnel Administration
    Notes: v.1 (1934:July 15)-v.4 (1938:July 1). Bound volume.
- National Foremen's Institute, 1957-1958 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Employer Relations Bulletin, 1957-1958 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    Author: National Foremen's Institute
    Notes: no.592 (1957:Aug. 28)-no.646 (1958:Dec. 24). Bound volume.
- Automobile Manufacturers Association, 1945; Publication (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Current Outlook, 1945; Publication (Box 17, Folder 7)
    Notes: no.1 (1945:Feb.)-no.12 (1945:Oct.). Bound volume.
- Automobile Manufacturers Association, 1946-1948 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Current Outlook, 1946-1948 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    Notes: no.24 (1946:May)-no.71 (1948:Apr.). Bound volume.
- California Packing Corporation, 1925-1932 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Del Monte Activities, 1925-1932 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    Author: Employees Activities Committee
    Notes: v.7:no.1 (1925:Mar.)-v.14:no.1 (1932:Mar.). Bound volume.
- National Foremen's Institute, 1959; Publication (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Employer Relations Bulletin, 1959; Publication (Box 18, Folder 1)
    Notes: no.647-694 (1959). Bound volume.
- National Foremen's Institute, 1960; Publication (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Employer Relations Bulletin, 1960; Publication (Box 18, Folder 2)
    Notes: no.695-742 (1960). Bound volume.
- National Foremen's Institute, 1961; Publication (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Employer Relations Bulletin, 1961; Publication (Box 18, Folder 3)
    Notes: no.743-790 (1961). Bound volume.
- National Foremen's Institute, 1962; Publication (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Employer Relations Bulletin, 1962; Publication (Box 18, Folder 4)
    Notes: no.791-838 (1962). Bound volume.
- National Foremen's Institute, 1963; Publication (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Employer Relations Bulletin, 1963; Publication (Box 18, Folder 5)
    Notes: no.839 (1963:Jan.)-no.856 (1963:May). Bound volume.
- Pennsylvania Department of Labor and Industry, 1943-1955 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Employment Conditions in Pennsylvania Industries, 1943-1955 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    Author: Bureau of Research and Information
    Notes: January, 1943-December, 1955. Bound volume.
- Labor Bureau, Inc., 1928-1930 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Facts For Workers, 1928-1930 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    Author: Labor Bureau, Inc.
    Notes: October, 1928- September, 1930. Bound volume.
- Canadian Pacific Railways, 1937-1943 (Box 19A, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Canadian Pacific Staff Bulletin, 1937-1943 (Box 19A, Folder 1)
    Author: Canadian Pacific Railways
    Notes: no.16 (1937)-no.96 (1943). Bound volume.
- H. J. Heinz Company, 1939-1947 (Box 19A, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: The 57 News, 1939-1947 (Box 19A, Folder 2)
    Author: H. J. Heinz Company
    Notes: January, 1939- December, 1947. Bound volume.
- H. J. Heinz Company, 1948-1952 (Box 19A, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: The 57 News, 1948-1952 (Box 19A, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.31 (1948)-v.35 (1952). Bound volume.
- H. J. Heinz Company, 1923-1931 (Box 19B, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: The 57 News, 1923-1931 (Box 19B, Folder 1)
    Notes: May, 1923 - Nov., 1931. Bound volume.
- H. J. Heinz Company, 1932-1937 (Box 19B, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: The 57 News, 1932-1937 (Box 19B, Folder 2)
    Notes: Jan., 1932 - May, 1937. Bound volume.
- H. J. Heinz Company, 1953-1960 (Box 19B, Folder 4)